(this.webpackJsonpclient=this.webpackJsonpclient||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(1),n=r.n(s),o=r(4),i=r.n(o),a=(r(9),r(2)),c=r(0);function w(){var e=[{questionText:"the skill, system, or job of keeping the financial records of a business or person",answerOptions:[{answerText:"boss",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"accounting",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"criminal",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"the person whose job is to tell other workers what to do ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"accounting",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"criminal",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"fire",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"boss",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"not angry, upset, excited, etc",answerOptions:[{answerText:"videographer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"calm",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"rumor",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"fire",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"an amount of money available for spending that is based on a plan for how it will be spent ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"update",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"scare",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"fire",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"budget",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"a person who has committed a crime or who has been proven to be guilty of a crime by a court ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"update",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"scare",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"criminal",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"fire",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"a police offi cer whose job is to fi nd information about crimes that have occurred and to catch criminals",answerOptions:[{answerText:"detective",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"update",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"criminal",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"budget",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"to dismiss (someone) from a job ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"budget",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"reset",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"scare",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"fire",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"information or a story that is passed from person to person but has not been proven to be true",answerOptions:[{answerText:"rumor",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"update",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"scare",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"fire",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"to cause (someone) to become afraid",answerOptions:[{answerText:"climb",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"update",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"scare",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"fire",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:" to change (something) by including the most recent information",answerOptions:[{answerText:"budget",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"fire",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"scare",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"update",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"a person who records images or events using a video camera",answerOptions:[{answerText:"budget",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"videographer",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"e-mail",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"dry",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"to talk about the personal lives of other people",answerOptions:[{answerText:"budget",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"e-mail",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"dry",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"gossip",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"used as an angry way to tell someone to leave, (def ol)",answerOptions:[{answerText:"come on",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"get out",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"help me",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"kick out",isCorrect:!1}]}],t=Object(s.useState)(0),r=Object(a.a)(t,2),n=r[0],o=r[1],i=Object(s.useState)(!1),w=Object(a.a)(i,2),x=w[0],u=w[1],T=Object(s.useState)(0),d=Object(a.a)(T,2),l=d[0],C=d[1];return Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:x?Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:["You scored ",l," out of ",e.length]}):Object(c.jsxs)(c.Fragment,{children:[Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(c.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",n+1]}),"/",e.length]}),Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:e[n].questionText})]}),Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[n].answerOptions.map((function(t){return Object(c.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&C(l+1);var r=n+1;r<e.length?o(r):u(!0)}(t.isCorrect)},children:t.answerText})}))})]})})}var x=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,12)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,s=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,o=t.getLCP,i=t.getTTFB;r(e),s(e),n(e),o(e),i(e)}))};i.a.render(Object(c.jsx)(n.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(c.jsx)(w,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),x()},9:function(e,t,r){}},[[11,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2f523b52.chunk.js.map